当你们的Marshall叔叔十岁时
When your Uncle Marshall was ten years old,
他读了本书叫《在大猩猩中生活》
he read a book called Life Among the Gorillas.
Aurelia Birnholz-Vazquez一个人类学博士所写
It was written by an anthropologist named Dr. Aurelia Birnholz-Vazquez,
讲的是她和喀麦隆的西部低地猩猩一起生活的经历
and it told the story of the year she spent living among the Western Lowland Gorillas of Cameroon.
Birnholz-Vazquez博士来地方大学办讲座
When Dr. Birnholz-Vazquez came to the local community college to give a lecture,
最年轻的听众Marshall举起了手提问
Marshall, the youngest member of the audience, raised his hand with a question.
你对未来的人类学家有什么建议?
What advice do you have for a budding anthropologist?
你想成为人类学家吗?
So you want to be an anthropologist?
对 我长大后要和你一样跟大猩猩一起生活
Yep. When I grow up, I want to go live with the gorillas, just like you did.
她接下来说的话改变了他的一生
What she said next changed his life.
噢, 不错, 但恐怕你不行了
Oh, that's wonderful, but I'm afraid you can't.
等你长大那时候猩猩已经死光了
They'll all be dead by then.
...如果不强制执行经济制裁和贸易管制
...and if economic sanctions and trade restrictions aren't enforced,
对雨林的破坏将会持续，超过百万的物种将会灭绝
the destruction of the rainforests will continue and over a million species will be wiped out.
所以你不要咖啡?
So you don't want coffee?
我在说咖啡工业将导致无法挽回的...
I'm saying that the coffee industry is causing irreversible...
- 好吧 我把它倒了\n- 好吧, 就一杯
- All right. I'm pouring it out.\n- Okay, one cup.
小朋友需要被警告，工作第一天得多加小心
The kid needs to be alert. First day on the job and everything.
我还是不敢相信你要去公司工作
I still can't believe you're going all corporate on us.
"男孩"已经成为"男人"了
"The kid" has become "the man."
好了, 这只是实习挣点钱
Okay, it's just an internship to make a little money.
毕业后, 我会去自然资源保护委员会工作
After law school, I'm going to work for the NRDC.
他们会阻止全球气候变暖
They're gonna stop global warming.
嗯... 我是说... 他们会尽全力
Well... I mean... they did their best.
你的外带午餐
Here's your sack lunch.
好了, 我爱你因为，第一, 你给我准备外带午餐
Okay, I love you because, one, you made me a sack lunch
第二, 你每次说"外带"时都会笑
and two, you laugh every time you say the word "sack".
- 我爱你, 棉花糖\n- 我爱你
- I love you, Marshmallow.\n- I love you.
我也爱你, 棉花糖
I love you too, Marshmallow.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
Ted?\nTed?
噢, 别 别, 她不是吧
Oh, no. No, she didn't.
是的 就是她
Yeah. Yeah, she did.
又一个关怀包裹?
Another care package?
又一个关怀包裹
Another care package.
我和Victoria异地恋持续了近一个月
I'd been in a long-distance relationship with Victoria for nearly a month.
异地恋真糟糕
Long-distance relationships are a bad idea.
到现在这是第几个了?
How many is that so far?
三
Three.
那你给她送了几个包裹?
And how many have you sent her?
电邮里还是脑子里?
In the mail or in my mind?
零，她却寄来了三个.
Zero. She's up three-zip.
噢! 纸托蛋糕!
Oh! Cupcakes!
真好 我打赌它们很可口
Great. I bet they're delicious, too.
对了, 它们很可口
Yep, they're delicious.
真该死!
Damn it!
我不配吃这些可口的纸托蛋糕
I don't deserve these delicious cupcakes.
天那, 我讨厌我自己
God, I hate myself right now.
天那, 简直和我15岁时一样
God, that is so me at 15.
Marshall要去一个叫Altrucel的公司工作
Marshall was going to work for a big corporation called Altrucel.
Altrucel以生产网球面上的黄绒毛著名
Altrucel was most well-known for making the yellow fuzzy stuff on the surface of tennis balls.
我是说, 这是一个大公司\n所以他们也有其他的生意...
I mean, this was a huge company, so they did other things...
但他们希望公众把注意力集中在那些黄绒毛上
But mostly they wanted the public to focus on the yellow fuzzy stuff.
Marshall在他们的法律部找到了实习机会
Anyway, Marshall managed to score an internship in their legal department
因为他认识那里工作的某人
because he knew someone who worked there.
这里是Barney
Go for Barney.
Stinson先生, 我是大厅保安Willis
Mr. Stinson, this is Willis from lobby security.
抱歉打扰您, 但是我们接到报告,有个大脚野人进了大楼
Sorry to bother you, but we've had reports of a sasquatch loose in the building.
大脚野人?
A sasquatch?
对, 先生, 脚很大
That's right, sir, a Bigfoot.
我们不想吓到您, 但他在您的楼层
We don't want to alarm you, but he's been spotted on your floor.
真好!
Yes!
看看你
Look at you.
你穿的很得体
You suited in an unmistakably upward direction.
哇哦 一大堆鼓舞人心的海报
Whoa. That is a butt-load of motivational posters.
是啊, 天, 是啊 我都有:合作, 勇气, 敬畏...
Yeah, hell, yeah. I got 'em all: Teamwork, Courage, Awesomeness...
有表示敬畏的吗?
There's one for awesomeness?
是啊, 我让人做的
Yeah, I had it made.
坐
Sit.
嘿, 那么, 现在我在这工作,你要告诉我到底你的工作是什么吗?
Hey, so, now that I'm working here, are you finally going to tell me exactly what your job is?
拜托
Please.
- 我们的狗!\n- 我们的狗!
- My dawg!\n- My dawg!
嘿, Blauman, Bilson, 这是Marshall.\n他们是法律部的
Hey, Blauman, Bilson, this is Marshall. These guys are in legal.
你要和他们一起工作
You're gonna be working with them.
Marshall Eriksen 很高兴认识你们
Marshall Eriksen. Nice to meet you.
领带不错 牛肉酱
Nice tie. Steak sauce.
噢, 牛肉酱! 真的
Oh, steak sauce! For true, though.
哪里, 我没, 我没看见啊...
Where, I don't, I don't see...
Marshall? 借一步说话
Marshall? Sidebar.
你的领带很牛肉酱 就是说很棒?\n懂了吗? 试着跟上进度
Your tie is steak sauce. It means A-1. A-1? Get it? Try to keep up.
好了, Eriksen, 我们开始吧\n凌晨两点 外面下着雨
Okay, Eriksen, let's get to work. \nIt's 2:00 a.m. It's raining outside.
叮咚! 什么? 门铃?
Ding dong! What? The doorbell?
噢, 你好, Jessica Alba就穿了件雨衣\n其他什么都没穿
Oh, hello, Jessica Alba in a trench coat and nothing else.
但等等 咚, 咚 后门有人敲门?
But wait-- knock, knock. Somebody's at the back door?
我家没后门
I don't have a back door.
噢, 我的老天,Jessica Simpson? 太惊喜了
Oh, my gosh, Jessica Simpson? What a surprise.
两个Jessica, 你得选一个,你会怎样? 选!
Two Jessicas, you gotta pick one. What do you do? Go.
好的, 呃... 我已经订婚了, 所以
Right. Well, uh... I'm engaged, so
未婚妻出城了 你会怎样?选
Fiancee's out of town. What do you do? Go.
但我们还是订着婚, 就算她...
We're still engaged, even if she's...
好吧, 未婚妻死了,被车撞的 你会怎样? 选
Okay, fiancee's dead. Hit by a bus. What do you do? Go.
确定不想吃一个?
Sure you don't want one?
你吃了多少了?
How  many of those have you eaten?
十...四\n不, 就四个
Four. Teen. No, just four.
还把另两个的糖霜刮了吃了
And the icing from two more.
所以, 无论如何, 这就是问题了
So, anyway, here's the problem.
嘿, 我是Ted,我猜你在睡觉
Hey, it's Ted. I guess you're asleep.
我收到关怀包裹了, 真是很棒
Anyway, I got the care package, and it's just great.
这儿, 听着...
Here, listen...
嗯 嗯!
Mmm. Mmm!
我就站在那儿,嘴巴塞满美味的纸托蛋糕...
So I'm standing there, my mouth full of this delicious relationship-winning cupcake...
然后... 我说了句蠢话
And... I said something dumb.
噢, 还有, 呃... 别担心,你的包裹我送出去了
Oh, and, um... don't worry, yours is in the mail.
我几天前送出去的
I sent it a couple days ago.
很不错的东西
And it's awesome.
真的, 真的很不错
Really, really awesome.
为什么我要说那些?
Why did I say that?
我想是糖精让我撒谎
I think frosting makes me lie.
噢, 小Teddy
Oh, Teddy boy.
是啊 所以现在, 不管我送她什么\n她都会发现我是在那之后送的
Yeah. So now, whatever I send her, \nshe'll know I sent it after I talked to her.
这就是问题 你想办法,我负责吃蛋糕
So that's the problem. You work on that. I'm gonna eat this cupcake.
好了, 你要做的是
All right, here's what you do:
打包一些纽约的东西进关怀包裹
Put together a care package of stuff from New York
一些面包圈, 帝国大厦钥匙圈...
some H&H bagels, an Empire State Building keychain...
然后在最上面放一份纽约时报... 知道吗?
and then, top off the package with a New York Times... Ready?
三天前的报纸
From three days ago.
这太妙了
That's  brilliant.
你真聪明
You're brilliant.
你知道吗, 这太搞笑了, 不久前
You know, it's funny, not so long ago,
我还去问Marshall和Lily如何打动你
I was coming to Marshall and Lily for advice on how to impress you.
是很搞笑
That is funny.
这就是为什么很搞笑
And here's why it was funny.
几周前我知道了
Little did I realize, a few weeks earlier,
Robin对Lily谈论我的内容
here's what Robin was saying to Lily about me.
好吧, 是, 我对他有感觉
Okay, fine, I have feelings for him.
真讽刺, 我以前喜欢的女孩帮我出主意追现在我喜欢的女孩
Now it's ironic, the girl I used to like is helping me impress the girl I now like.
明显很讽刺, Ted
The irony is clear, Ted.
嘿! 第一天怎么样?
Hey! How was your first day?
我不想再提了
I don't wanna talk about it.
和我一起工作的那帮家伙是群蠢人
The guys I work with are a bunch of jerks.
- 什么?\n- 他们是笨蛋!
- What?\n- They're jerks!
为什么他们很蠢?
What makes them jerks?
算了, 我不想再提了
Forget it, I don't want to talk about it.
嗯, 今天午餐时..
Well, like today at lunch..
里面有什么, Ericksen?\n妈咪给你打包的午餐?
What do you got there, Ericksen? \nMommy pack your lunch?
仅为告知, 我未婚妻做的
For your information, my fiancee did.
噢... 她也帮你把土司皮给去了吧?
Oh... Does she cut the crusts off your sandwich, too?
没
No.
那是什么?
What's that?
没什么
Nothing.
拿来
Give it.
"亲爱的棉花糖 祝你好运，我爱你 百合花"
"Dear Marshmallow. Good luck today. I love you. Lilypad."
拿来
Give it.
另外 我给你的吻会在你打开这张字条时飞出来 快接住"
P.S. If you've unfolded this note, your kiss already got out. Quick-- catch it."
还给我 嘿, 拿来 给我... 还给我!
Give it back. Hey, give it. Give me... Give it!
噢, 这些坏家伙! 我们那么可爱
Oh, screw those guys! We're adorable.
我知道 天那
I know. God.
就象又回到当新生时
It's like freshman year all over again.
只是这次, 我的舞蹈搞不定他们了
Only this time, my sweet dance moves aren't going to be enough to win them over.
机器人舞也不行
Not even Old Reliable.
甜心... 弄点外快确实不错
Sweetie... It would be cool to have some extra money,
但, 但是, 如果你不开心, 就不值得了
but, but, if you're unhappy, it's not worth it.
我辞职
I quit.
什么? 不行 我们一起会很好玩的
What? No. We're having so much fun.
你, 我, 一起工作 太棒了
You, me, working together. It's great.
我们根本没一起工作, Barney,我在法律部而你...
We're not even working together, Barney. I'm in the legal department and you're...
说真的, 你到底是做什么的?
Seriously, what is it that you do?
拜托
Please.
抱歉, 兄弟, 公司的工作,这个... 不适合我
I'm sorry, dude, this corporate thing, it's just... it's not for me.
噢, 当然不是为了你自己
Oh, of course it's not for you.
这是为了Lily
It's for Lily.
什么?
What?
Marshall, Lily很抢手
Marshall. Lily's a catch.
你真的以为可以没福利就和一个这么好的女孩在一起?
But do you really think you're going to hang onto a girl that great without the package?
福利?
The package?
福利: 房子, 车, 把孩子送进好学校
The package. The house. The car. Sending your kids to a great school.
偶尔渡个假
A vacation once in a while.
Lily不在乎这些
Lily doesn't care about that stuff.
嗯, 现在她不在乎, 但几年后呢?
Well, no-- now she doesn't, but how's she going to feel in a couple years,
当她在用幼儿园教师的薪水供养你
when she's supporting you on a kindergarten teacher's salary
你却在法庭上为那些濒临灭绝的...南美...飞海狸辩护时
while you're off in court defending some... endangered... South American... flying beaver.
她会开心的
She'll be happy.
好吧
Okay.
但当你知道你可以让她更开心，不感到开心吗
But will you be happy knowing you could have made her a lot happier.
四个都是裸体的 你得挑一个，你会怎样? 选
And all four are totally naked. You gotta choose one. What do you do? Go.
我猜, 呃...
I guess, uh...
Bea Arthur\nBea Arthur.
啊! 错! Betty White
Ahh! Wrong! Betty White.
把这里收拾干净, Eriksen
Clean this stuff up, Eriksen.
那她收到关怀包裹了吗?
So, did she get the awesome care package yet?
嗯 昨天
Yep. Yesterday.
她喜欢吗?
Did she love it?
噢, 她很喜欢
Oh, she loved it.
那有什么问题?
So what's the problem?
我昨天和她聊天了 我得申明
So I was talking to her last night. And, I should tell you,
我们每隔一天就讲差不多一个半小时电话
we've been talking on the phone every other night for, like, an hour and a half.
渐渐的没有什么话题可说了
Eventually you just run out of stuff to say.
今天午餐吃了什么?
What did you have for lunch today?
噢 黑麦面包
Oh. Rye bread.
耶
Yeah.
噢, 小Teddy
Oh, Teddy boy.
我一般都会是个好男友的，但是这样见不了面, 真糟糕
I'm usually so good at being a boyfriend, but this never-seeing-each-other thing, it's a bitch.
也许这样行不通
Maybe it just can't be done.
我想我该做什么很明显了
I think it's clear what I have to do.
很明显
It's pretty clear.
我要去德国给她一个惊喜
I have to go to Germany and surprise her.
完全和我想的一样
Totally what I was thinking.
滚出我脑袋, 伙计!
Get out of my head, man!
Barney, 我该怎么让那些白痴离我远点?
Barney, how do I get these idiots to leave me alone?
Marshall,  想想企鹅
Marshall,  consider the penguins.
企鹅?
The penguins?
在墙上
On the wall.
"团结 才能抵御寒冷"
"Conformity. It's the one who's different that gets left out in the cold."
这是激励人的海报吗?
This is a motivational poster?
看看你自己, Marshall你不开心
Look at yourself, Marshall. You're not happy.
知道为什么吗? 因为你和他们不一样
And you know why? Because you're different.
现在, 你要么自怨自艾
Now, I suppose you could learn to love yourself for the unique little snowflake that you are,
要么... 你可以改变你的性格，这样比较简单
or... you could change your entire personality, which is just so much easier.
改变个性? 太糟糕了，而且也不能激励人
Change your personality? That is so awful, and not at all motivational.
没必要 好吧, 开始, 我很沮丧
Not necessarily. Okay, at first, I was appalled,
但是后来我发现这就象Aurelia Birnholz\nVasquez博士在猩猩中生活一样
but then I realized it's just like Dr. Aurelia Birnholz-Vasquez in Life Among the Gorillas.
要变的跟它们一样，才能的到群体的认同
I have to gain the acceptance of the herd by behaving exactly like one of them.
这是个人类学课题 酷不?
It's an anthropological study. Isn't that cool?
这听起来更象外界压力吧
It  sounds kinda like peer pressure.
不, 不, 不 这绝对是人类学
No, no, no. It's totally anthropological
而且我就在做这件很酷的事
and it's cool and I'm doing it.
耶, 我确定这就是外界压力\n我们每年都有同学聚会
Yeah, I'm pretty sure it's peer pressure. \nWe have an assembly every year.
我是在扮演向外界压力屈从的人
I'm portraying someone who succumbs to peer pressure.
好吧, 如果这些家伙逼你抽烟，你会怎么说?
All right, but if those guys try to pressure you to smoke, what do you say?
- 除非我喝醉了\n- 乖孩子
- Only when I'm drunk.\n- Good boy.
所以, 要和猩猩一起生活\nMarshall首先得做的像猩猩
And so, to fit in with the gorillas, Marshall had to learn to act like a gorilla,
这就意味着学习猩猩课程
and that meant gorilla lessons.
好了, 我真兴奋
Okay, I'm psyched about this.
但如果我要来教你，我得知道你现在也很兴奋
But if I'm going to mentor you, I need to know you're psyched about this, too.
噢, 我是 我是很兴奋
Oh, I am. I'm, I'm psyched.
耶, 但是不仅要说，还要表现出你很兴奋
Yeah, but it's one thing to say it, it's another thing to show it.
秀出来
Show it.
我很兴奋!
I'm psyched!
那是什么?
What was that?
Marshall, 我要感觉到大把的激情冲击过来
Marshall, I should feel tremors of psychitude rock my body like a seizure.
就象一只被去掉猫爪的怀孕了的猫
That was like a declawed pregnant cat on a porch swing idly swatting
在周六下午懒散的躺在秋千上拍苍蝇
at a fly on a lazy Sunday afternoon.
哇, 讲的真精辟
Wow, that was really specific.
给我看看你的激情!
Show me you're psyched!
来吧!
Let's do this!
- 啊! 真痛!\n- 确实
- Ow! That hurt!\n- So badly.
然后你小心的把这个在握手时给他就搞定了
And then you slip it to the guy with a discreet handshake and he'll get it done.
好的 搞定什么?
Right. Get what done?
随便什么
Whatever.
酷
Cool.
那搞定哪个家伙呢?
And what guy is this?
总会有的
There's always a guy.
好了, 好的, 呃, 我想我准备好了
Okay, all right, I, uh, I think I'm ready.
确定? 你要再练习一遍吗?
You sure? You want to practice your story one more time?
好吧
All right.
那伙计, 听着 我和两个Kappa的员工在圣地亚哥
So dude, check it. I'm in San Diego with two of my bro-sephs from Kappa,
他们说, "哟, Eriksen我们去脱衣舞俱乐部吧"
and they're all, "Yo, Eriksen, let's roll to the strip clubs."
然后我说, "说干就干!"
So I'm, like, "Snapadoo!"
所以我们找到了机场附近的黄窝...
So we find this choice nudie nest near the airport...
...就在这时保镖把我们赶出来了
...and that is when the bouncer kicked us out.
现在我也不知道Svetlana拿到绿卡没\n但伙计们, 假钻戒?
Now, I have no idea if Svetlana ever got her green card, \nbut dudes, fake diamond ring?
绝对物超所值, 兄弟
Worth every penny, bruh.
Eriksen...\nEriksen...
...绝对是牛肉酱!
...that was steak sauce!
好故事
Great story.
第二天早晨我订去德国的机票时收到一封邮件
The next moning, I was about to buy my ticket to Germany when I got an e-mail.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
"嘿, Ted, 抱歉昨晚错过了你的电话
"Hey, Ted, sorry I missed your call last night.
异地恋真糟糕, 是不?
This long-distance thing sucks, huh?
听着, 我考虑了下，我今晚需要和你谈谈
Listen, I've been thinking and I really need to talk to you tonight.
我晚上十一点打给你 Victoria"
I'll call you at 11:00. Victoria."
所以?
So?
所以她要甩了我
So she's going to dump me.
有人会在说过, "听着, 我考虑了下"
Has anyone ever said, "Listen, I've been thinking,"
然后接着说的是好消息吗?
and then follow it up with something good?
不是像: 听着, 我考虑了下果仁奶油饼干是评价较低的饼干
It's not like: Listen, I've been thinking, Nutter-Butters are an underrated cookie.
还能是什么呢?
What else can it be?
有什么她不能在邮件里说而要打电话的?
What could she possibly have to say to me that she couldn't write in an e-mail?
我手指被切掉了?
I cut off all my fingers?
Ted, 你是个不错的家伙，我知, 你知, 她也知
Ted, you're a great guy. I know it, you know it, she knows it.
我愿意赌上大把的钱\n不, 我应该更自信点\nI would bet you a gazillion dollars，
no, I'm even more confident.
我赌上所有的钱 她不是打电话说要和你分手
I would bet you a floppity jillion dollars that she's not calling to break up with you.
谢谢 你是对的 我要疯了
Thanks. You're right. I'm being crazy.
所以我还是去买机票, 是不?
So I should still buy that plane ticket, right?
我会等等看
I'd wait.
在吃饭吗, Blauman? 我是电子炸弹
Sup, Blauman? E-bomb here.
我们要去卡拉ok吗?
We still on for karaoke?
伙计 我要用麦克风震的你喷鼻血
Dope. I'm going to rock you on the mike so hard your hears are going to bleed gravy.
到时见, 屁股仔!
Catch you on the flip, butt puppet.
好了...
Okay...
...怎么样?
...what do you think?
牛肉酱
Steak sauce.
牛肉酱?
Steak sauce?
耶
Yeah.
不管你用什么人类学在工作上都不关我的事
Look, you know, whatever anthropology you do at work is your business,
但别在家里也这样
but please don't act like that around here.
Lily, 当Aurelia Birnholz博士...
Lily, when Dr. Aurelia Birnholz...
不对, 当Australia Birdbath-Vaseline博士\n从猩猩们那里回来时
No, when Dr. Australia Birdbath-Vaseline came home from the gorillas,
她不会到处抓人们头发上的虱子和乱丢粪便
she didn't run around picking nits out of people's hair and-and throwing feces.
我求你把这些留在办公室吧
I'm begging you just, just leave it at the office.
为什么?
Why?
因为你表现的和那些家伙一样\n这些家伙很讨厌
Because you're acting like one of those guys, \nand those guys are lame.
好吧, 他们开始是对我很刻薄
Okay, those guys were mean at first, yes,
但他们是不错的人，如果你去了解下他们就会知道了
but they're actually good guys, and if you got to know them, then you would see that.
今晚和我们一起去卡拉ok你就会发现他们没那么讨厌了, 好不?
Come karaoke with us tonight, and you'll see how totally not that lame they are, okay?
好吧
Okay.
但等等, 咚咚, 后门有人敲门, 是谁呢?
But wait, knock-knock, back door, who's there?
Angelina Jolie... 等下，坐在轮椅里
Angelina Jolie... wait, in a wheelchair.
你会怎样? 回答
What do you do? Go.
伙计, 缺胳膊的Scarlett Johannsen每天都有
Dude, Scarlett Johannsen with no arms, any day of the week.
耶
Yeah.
你对了 他们真是不错
You're right. They're delightful.
那Barney, 你要唱吗?
So, Barney, you gonna sing anything?
不要了 我玩腻卡拉ok了
Nah. I'm so over karaoke.
是吗? 我以为你很喜欢玩这个
Really? I thought you'd be totally into it.
噢, 别理解错了 我唱的很好，最好的, 真的
Oh, don't get me wrong. I'm good. The best, really.
我是让刀锈在鞘里的最伟大的武士
But it's the greatest samurai who lets his sword rust in its scabbard.
噢, 宝贝, 这儿有我们的歌
Oh, baby, they have our song.
我们来唱"别伤我的心"吧
Let's do "Don't Go Breaking My Heart."
什么?
What?
"别伤我的心"Elton John和Kiki Dee唱的
"Don't Go Breaking My Heart." Elton John, Kiki Dee.
没门 你们得唱黑色安息日乐队的歌
No way. You got to go with some Black Sabbath.
恩, 事实上, Marshall和我还有段小舞蹈
Well, actually, Marshall and I have this little dance routine.
"机器人" 我可以唱 "机器人"
"Iron Man." I could do "Iron Man."
牛肉酱
Steak sauce.
牛肉酱, 伙计
Steak sauce, dude.
我们要告诉他吗?
Should we tell him?
好了, Eriksen, 我有个好消息
All right, Eriksen, I've got some good news.
周一, Bilson和我要和人力部的Montague谈
On Monday, Bilson and I are going to talk to Montague in HR.
你毕业后，我们想请你和我们一起工作
When you graduate, we want you working with us.
你说什么?
What do you say?
- 好!\n- 这才是我们的男人!
- Yes!\n- That's my man!
我就说他会的
I told you he would.
啊, 我们要称霸办公室了
Aw, we're gonna own the office.
好吧, 太讨厌了
Okay, that was gross.
你准备什么时候告诉我你改变了你整个就业计划?
When were you going to tell me you changed your entire career path?
没有什么改变了, 好吗?我还是想支持环保事业
Nothing has changed, okay? I still want to help the environment.
我只是在想也许我可以先挣几年钱
I just thought that maybe I could make some money for a few years.
可以买间公寓，把我们的孩子送进好学校
We could buy an apartment, send our kids to good schools.
你可以不用工作, 专心绘画
You could quit your job and focus on your painting.
我知道你说你不需要, 但是...
I know that you say you don't need it, but...
我爱你如论如何都想给你这些
I love you and I want to give it to you anyway.
我想给你挣来那些福利
I want to give you the package.
福利?! 你已经给我了福利了
The package?! You've already given me the package.
你给了我很棒的福利 Marshall\n我喜欢你的"福利"
You've got a great package, Marshall. \nI love your package.
Lily, 你是让人难以置信的女人，你应该享有一份"大福利"
Lily, you're the most incredible woman I know, and you deserve a big package.
你的"福利"一直都够大了
Your package has always been big enough.
也许你没意识到, Marshall Eriksen
You may not realize this, Marshall Eriksen,
但你有个硕大的"福利"
but you've got a huge package.
是啊
Yeah.
喂
Hello.
她怎么还没打来?
Why hasn't she called yet?
好了, 你要把自己逼疯了，现在是周六晚上
Okay, you're making yourself crazy. It's Saturday night.
出去干点什么
Go out and do something.
不, 我出去干什么?\n我有女朋友了... 到现在为止
No, what's the point of going out? \nI got a girlfriend... for now.
另外, 如果我出去了, 谁看你播的新闻?\n我相当于你的一半观众
Besides, if I go out, who's going to watch the news? \nI'm, like, half your viewership.
我真荣幸你认为我有两个观众
I'm flattered you think we have two viewers.
她不会和你分手的，Ted 你很棒
She's not going to break up with you, Ted. You're awesome.
谢谢
Thanks.
不管怎样, 11:00点了 我得让你挂了
Anyway, it's almost 11:00. I should let you go.
祝你好运
Break a leg.
然后我坐在家里, 等着电话响，我想到了什么
And so I was sitting at home, waiting for the phone to ring, something occurred to me.
我就真在这坐着一直等着电话响
I'm actually sitting at home waiting for the phone to ring.
He's giving you the blues\nHe's giving you the blues
You want to graduate, but not in his bed\nYou want to graduate, but not in his bed
Here's what you got to do\nHere's what you got to do
Pick up the phone...\nPick up the phone...
Marshall\nMarshall.
嘿, 嘿
Hey, hey.
伙计, 我好象一个月没见你了
Dude, I feel like I haven't seen you in a month.
耶
Yeah.
过的怎么样?
How are you doing?
我想Victoria要和我分手了
I think Victoria's about to break up with me.
噢, 天那, 抱歉, 伙计
Oh, God, I'm sorry, man.
耶, 嗯, 说实话，我连想起她的长相都有困难了
Yeah, well, honestly, I'm having trouble remembering what she looks like.
越努力去想, 越想不出来
The more I try to picture her, the more I can't.
就象, 我还记得她给我的感觉
Like, I remember how she makes me feel.
我只是不能完全的回忆起她的样貌
I just... I don't completely remember her.
就象我在试图留住一些已经逝去了的东西
It's like I'm trying to preserve something that's already gone.
留住一些已经逝去了的东西
Preserving something that's already gone.
听起来象环境保护法
Sounds like environmental law.
我不知道
I don't know.
我们用尽全力去保住这些
We struggle so hard to hold onto these things
注定最终会消逝的东西
that we know are going to disappear eventually.
这样是很高尚
And that's really noble,
但如果你救回了每一片变成停车场的雨林
but even if you save every rainforest from being turned into a parking lot,
嗯, 那我们把车停哪儿呢?
well, then where are you going to park your car?
Done dirt cheap!\nDone dirt cheap!
Dirty deeds\nDirty deeds
Dirty deeds and they're done dirt cheap, ow\nDirty deeds and they're done dirt cheap, ow
Dirty deeds and they're done dirt cheap...\nDirty deeds and they're done dirt cheap...
啊, 正要到高潮. 伙计, 什么...?
Uh,  rockupied. Dude, what...?
下一首, 棉花糖和百合花
Next up, Marshmallow and Lillypad.
Don't go breakin' my heart\nDon't go breakin' my heart
I couldn't if I tried\nI couldn't if I tried
Honey, if I get restless\nHoney, if I get restless
Baby, you're not that kind...\nBaby, you're not that kind...
似乎还是有些东西值得去挽留的
It turns out some things are worth preserving.
但是还有个问题
But here's the real question:
凌晨两点 朋友们还在外面唱卡拉
It's 2:00 a.m. Your friends are still out singing karaoke,
但你却得提前回家等着本应该四个小时前
but you're home early because you're expecting a call from your girlfriend in Germany,
打来的在德国的女友的电话
who was supposed to call four hours ago.
然后电话响了
And then the phone rings.
喂
Hello.
嗨, Ted 我是Robin
Hi, Ted. It's Robin.
呃, 听着, 我知道现在很晚了, 但, 呃
Um, listen, I know it's late, but, uh,
你愿意过来吗?
do you want to come over?
你会怎样? 回答
What do you do? Go.